(Sheldon:)From this moment forward,
we can be roommates...
(Sheldon:)...but we will no longer be friends.
(Leonard:)I'm sorry you feel that way.
(Sheldon:)I don't think you're fully aware
of the ramifications here, Leonard.
[LEONARD SIGHS]
(Leonard:)Why don't you enlighten me?
(Sheldon:)With the friendship clause
of our agreement nullified...
...you're no longer entitled
to accompany me to go swimming...
(Sheldon:)...at Bill Gates' house
should I be invited.
(Howard:)Ooh, that's gotta sting.
(Leonard:)Think, this time tomorrow,
we'll be in Geneva, Switzerland...
(Leonard:)-...for our first Valentine's Day.
-I know.
(Penny:)I went shopping today and bought
special undies for the occasion.
Thermal? Because it's gonna be cold.
(Penny:)Think it through, Leonard.
(Leonard:)-Oh.
-Oh.
[BOTH LAUGH]
[SNEEZING]
(Leonard(Penny sneezes):)Gesundheit.
(Leonard(Penny sneezes):)Or as they say in Switzerland,
gesundheit.